you know when things take a long time
they're wondering you know maybe this is
not going to get done they're they're
not they're a little bit disinterested
they're not really quite sure what's
going on so it's my job to keep them
motivated it's my job to to chat I mean
to um least connect with them every few
days or or at least or at least every
three
days so uh just one second I'm just
going to see if we got people in the
room here um so shout out to Carrie
she's still here and um and folks if you
guys are tuning in for the first time
make sure to hit the the like buttons
and uh um and and be sure to share this
out because we're gonna have a eventful
conf and we're live how are you guys
doing folks this is go live and prosper
brought to you by hustle Zone TV um I
just want to thank you guys all for
tuning in tonight um and of course um
with all due respect make sure to um to
share this post out so I'm just going to
share this out to all of uh hold on one
second just gonna share it out we got
Carrie in the house what's going on
Carrie make sure you guys share it out
to all your
friends it would be truly appreciated
and um I'm going to share it out on my
phone so how are you guys been doing oh
oh you don't want to see that you don't
want to see that uh how are you guys
doing today uh welcome to go live life
and prosper and as you guys know you
know we've been doing this show um this
series like we're going on to our I
think fourth
year I think I think I I haven't really
counted the days when I started the show
but you know it's been you know we've
we've interviewed over 30 entrepreneurs
and um and we've all heard everyone
everyone's different stories so you know
we have an amazing individual on today
and his name is Antoine Watson we are
going to talk to him about his
successful business venture uh he has a
fullservice commercial construction loan
brokerage firm um he's getting married
and he has a new son and business is
going well for him so we're g to bring
him onto the screen so that he can tell
us his story so how's it going Antoine
it's it's going great um first of all
let me just thank you for me the
opportunity to be on the
broadcast yeah most definitely and thank
you thank you definitely for for for
reaching out so I want to know
everything about who you are how you got
here uh but the first question uh just
to um to explain to our audience you
know what's your business uh what do you
guys do well um again uh like like you
like you mentioned we are we are a
commercial loan brokerage uh the focus
the focus of our business is is uh
helping um commercial construction uh
commercial real estate uh companies and
and professional to be able to get
financing for their projects so um
typically typically our our range of
projects or right around $10 million up
to about 800 800 million and so we're
and so we W so so over the last few
years we built a lot of relationships
with different lending Partners so all
the financing that we do is outside of
your traditional banking so it's all
done through um it's alternative
finances so it's all done through
private lenders private money lenders um
private Equity venture
capitalist
wow so sorry about that uh so tell me
for a lot of us that are new to like are
do you only do busst to business or do
you business to
Consumer um I I I mean um a lot of times
you know our our main focus a lot of
times is commercial um but we're we're
exposed to a lot of different um
opportunities um but a lot of times it's
it's not really um you know businesses
to Consumer a lot of times it is it is
business to business um and that's the
thing we we started we started actually
a few years back and when we first
started we were doing all different
types of businesses um at that time we
didn't really have a niche But as time
went on and we did our research we did
our homework we realized that the areas
we really wanted to focus on was
commercial real estate and commercial
construction but we we wanted to focus
on ground level commercial construction
so we wanted to be able to finance the
building when it was when it was at at
ground
level and you know for for a lot of guys
because I mean a lot of people are
talking about real estate investing and
you know a lot of people don't know
where to start and you know you you you
you hear these things like zero down and
um you know you have these concepts of
zero down you have a lot of people
wanting to get in to use other people's
money to start you know these projects
and and you know how how would you if
someone was asking for your mentorship
where would you tell someone to
start well um you know one I I I'll just
tell them one to to do their homework um
there's a lot of people out there that's
uh I mean alternative financing is
definitely growing over the last few
years and there lot there a lot of
people out there that's doing it uh but
you got you got to do your homework and
you gota you got to make sure that
you're getting the right lending company
the right lender to work with you
because there's there's so many
different types of lenders and so many
lenders that require uh different things
um but if if there's someone out there I
would always recommend watching capital
and and the reason is is that we we not
only help you get the financing but we
do everything from A to Z to help you
get to financing so it's a lot of things
on our end we have to help you to do we
we make we take a look at your project
we make we make sure that that that the
way the way that is the way that is
defined it it makes sense and then once
we do that we we make sure you have all
your documentation and then once we do
that our job is to make sure we could be
able to sell your project to our lending
partners and and and not only that a lot
of times you know the the the typical uh
project that we do we it typically takes
us about three months to get our clients
financing and so we we also keep them
motivated because because that's one of
the things you got to do because a lot
of times people you know when things
take a long time they're wondering you
know maybe this is not going to get done
they're they're not they're a little bit
disinterested they're not really quite
sure what's going on so it's my job to
keep them motivated it's my job to to
chat I mean to um at least connect with
them every few days or or at least or at
least every three
days so uh just one second I'm just
going to see if we got people in the
room here um so shout out to Carrie
she's still here and um and folks if you
guys are tuning in for the first time
make sure to hit the the like buttons
and uh U and and be sure to share this
out because we're going to have a
eventful conversation today so uh so
Antoine now uh without that being said
this is UNT traditional for me to ask
about the business first but I wanted
people just to get a scope of what you
do but the real question is how did you
get to this position in your life where
you
know that you you're you're connecting
people to lending Partners Etc You're
Building uh commercial real estate you
know what is your story well I I got to
be honest with you nothing I'm doing was
ever planned you know um the thing about
me my whole journey has been
perseverance it's been beating the odds
you know it's been working hard doing
everything possible you know believing
in myself believing in God you know so
it's it's it's been a fight but um all
of it all of it's been worth it you know
uh but my my journey started you know
fighting through
childhood um as I was as I was uh
diagnosed with a learning disability
that was the that was my first fight in
life and that was a fight because no
matter how hard I worked in school you
know going to tutoring doing every every
single thing possible you know it was a
struggle for me academically to to get
the grades that that the other kids were
getting and because I dealt with uh with
this learning disability it it really
messed with my confidence so I didn't
have the confidence to build a lot of
friendships because I felt like I was
different and with me dealing with that
I mean it was going to be really
difficult for me to for me to make any
kind of friendship so I stayed to myself
pretty much and um as time went on you
know a lot of the professionals at at
the school started giving me you know
different different help you know taking
me outside of the classroom and and
really giving me that oneon-one help and
that one-onone help go ahead yeah sorry
I don't mean to interrupt um hold on one
sec sorry my phone is buzzing today but
um the one in-one help what what
learning disabil ability did you
have well um The Learning the learning
disability I had is you know I I no
matter I mean if it was a certain
subject that was going on in the class
whether it was math
English most kids that can get it on the
first go round you you show them
something in front of them and they they
got it me it took it took maybe five or
six times and and and even even on the
five or six times I still wasn't
confident like I had it and so that that
that affected my
grades but what what they started doing
at the school was they started taking me
out and putting me in these resources
classes so what they started doing was
they started shrinking my the
assignments I was doing and that gave me
it took the pressure off a little bit
because I started started being able to
do a little bit and I started building a
little bit of confidence in me and of
course you know when I started going
when I started going into this resource
Class A lot of the kids a lot of the
students were asking me you know where
you going they were asking me all these
questions and I and I wasn't confident I
wasn't um I didn't really want to you
know let people know what's going on I
was pretty private and everything like
that so I never I never really told them
what was going on but you know they they
kind of started putting their own
opinions about me so
you like I had um I like like that's why
I called myself brand Savant because um
I had a learning disability when I was
growing up and um they call it dyslexia
and I had a disc calcula as well um just
not being able to knowing like I I knew
I I thought I was smart but I wasn't
smart when I talked and I wasn't smart
when I wrote and I wasn't smart when I
was reading certain things I couldn't
comprehend those Concepts and at the
time when I was growing up like there
was not and maybe like you know you can
understand like like in the 80s and the
early 90s they didn't really have much
resources to really diagnose you to be
able to have you know what I mean for
you to be able to be confident in in
doing your your work because a lot of it
is that you know I think prior to 2000s
the school systems they were just kind
of designed for you to rot learn they
just said hey here's the book you read
it you memorize it and you should be
able to regurgitate it and you know
they're starting to find out now that
you know that type of method of learning
doesn't work so you know I totally
understand where you're coming from
because like we are all different in our
own ways that's why I say Savant because
we have our own genius we have our own
ways of looking at life all ways of uh
tapping into that internal
person that that guides you that helps
you make good decisions so what was your
your internal genius that you discovered
within yourself going through that
process well let let me tell you this um
as I was as I was um starting to build
my confidence you know with the resource
classes uh the turning point for me
actually
was discovering the game of
basketball um that right there it gave
me more confidence I built so many
relationships and as I started building
these relationships I was like you know
I'm just I'm just like the rest of these
guys I'm just like the rest of these
guys and they started they started
seeing I could play basketball and and I
started building so much respect and you
know from then on I never had any issues
with building relationships I never had
any issue with people talking about me
behind my back or anything like that and
you know the game of basketball it it
took me so many places I mean it it took
me from you know starting out in in in
the fourth grade playing basketball it
took me it took me overseas it took me
you know o over there over to uh Korea
Germany playing playing in high school
you know in the early
2000s you know it it took me all the way
over there and I I I stayed with the
game of I stayed with the game of
basketball until I was about 20 years
old and
you know then I I discovered that I I
didn't have the the passion for it my my
passions you know started to kind of
leave me and um you know that that right
there was was the first time that I felt
stuck in my entire life because you know
keep in mind I started at at at eight
and here I am 20 years old you know I
got I gotta figure out what what I'm
going to do with the rest of my life
because all all my life was once I once
I found out was was basketball
you know work all my the way I worked
out the way I the way I ate the way I
slept it was all basketball so you know
for the next probably 10 years you know
I went through life you know playing the
guessing game and trying to figure out
you know what I wanted to do you know I
I um I went through college but never
had a never had a degree I I went
through a I went to a small community
college you know and and got a got a
certificate in which I never really used
and um right right around that time it
was it was a mentor of mine that said
you know why don't you try why don't you
try sales you know you you can you could
do sales and um and make a lot of money
without having to have a degree so you
know I found I found myself I found
myself being a Salesman so I I did
inside sales for the next you know 10
years you know learning learning so much
information and it was right around this
time that I was doing the sales training
20 years old that I discovered that I
wanted to be an entrepreneur I wanted to
I wanted to uh you know be a business
owner and start building businesses so I
started there you know building my first
business I had a um had a basketball
training business you know which I which
I did for about for about three years
and keep in mind I didn't even have my
own facility for three years W yeah for
for three years I I use a outside court
with a roof over the top and had the
same client that stayed with me for
three years
wow now like what what made you say well
while you're doing sales on the phone
like what gave you the gumption to be
like hey I want to be an entrepreneur
because you know the definition of
entrepreneur is someone that wants to
endure the risk why you why did you want
to venture into that you start off with
you know having a learning disability
you go off to to be a a basketball
player and now you're in sales and then
you're like okay you know what this is
my calling this is where I'm GNA go well
it was it was one of those things
because see you got to understand in in
sales you're around a lot of people I
mean I was making I was the type of
phone calls I was making I was making
phone calls for a lot of business owners
you know individuals that were in
Insurance you know real estate all these
all these different types of
Industries and I got I got to the point
early in my life and I was like you know
I'm making these cold calls for somebody
else and I'm like why I mean imagine
what I could do for
myself so from then on I I spent a lot
of time like I said building these
businesses and and let me tell you I I I
went through a lot of failure with the I
went through a lot of failure with these
businesses because these businesses even
though I started them a lot of them
didn't a lot of them didn't really pan
out but I wasn't I wasn't discouraged
oh so hold on one second here sorry you
pause there for a second so you weren't
discouraged so how many businesses did
you
have well um I I gotta tell you
I I I I probably failed at probably
eight different businesses before I
finally
succeeded eight different
businesses that's a lot of businesses
well well like I said said um you know
I've always been one of those people
I've always been a fighter you know I've
always I've always been a person that
could persevere and I knew I was called
to be an entrepreneur and my thing was
it was it was more about me maturing as
an individual it was more about me uh
maturing as as a Christian and learning
about faith and it was it was me just
getting around the the right group of
people when it came to to building a
business you know
so it took me until up until now you
know to finally to finally reach the
success but you know I always see people
you know on social media and you know
social media makes things seem like it's
like it's overnight but I always let
people know that my over my overnight
success took 15 years it it took 15
years because it was it was so much I
had to
endure and I didn't at the time I was
frustrated but I I had to realize and
understand as I started kind of really
looking at the situation that I had to
be equipped for the the the the um the
journey that the guy was taking me on in
the Des in the destiny that he had for
me he had to prepare me and I I was I
wasn't prepared so I had to go through
these things I had to go through these
trials um the current the current
business I have right now Watson
worldwide capital you know a lot of
people don't know this but I built this
business while being an Uber
driver I
mean w waking up every morning what are
you talking about you were a Uber driver
and you decided to start this business
while you were driving Uber how okay you
gotta tell me that story okay well the
thing is um you know as as I matur
I I started finding direction because
like I Shar with you like I shared with
you early I was playing the guessing
game for a long time because I did not
know so right if you don't know
something you got to keep trying
different things until you until you
figure something out and so when I when
I started when I started sitting down
and reflecting and really saying okay
what is it that you want to do with your
life I realized that I realized that my
my goal in life was I wanted to be a
consultant and so what I started doing
was I started working backwards I said
okay you want to be a consultant what
are some things you could do that's
going to put you in that position so I
say okay wow I said Financial Services I
didn't I didn't know much about
financial services so I started doing my
research okay what part of financial
services and I said well wait a minute
there's people out here with businesses
there's people out here that need
Capital there's people out here that
cannot start businesses because they
don't have capital and what happens when
somebody start what happens when
somebody wants to start a business and
don't have Capital they never started
because they say okay the thing that
stopped me was the capital so that's
when I said Okay I I found a problem
that I could be able to solve and I just
had to I just had to educate
myself on on this industry and so I did
and like I said I was I was a Uber
driver as I was building this business
uh my my my thing was um every morning I
was getting at about 3:00 in the morning
driving Uber I would do 3:00 a.m. to
about 9 or 10: a.m. and I'm and then
about 10:00 in the morning I'm I'm back
at the office making cold calls doing
every every single thing possible to
learn this industry contacting um
private lenders contacting different
lending partners and so at at that time
Watson World white Capital was was not
what it is today at that time it was
more of me getting a group of friends
that I um had connected with in college
and we were trying to put we we were
both trying to put this this business
together and long story short you know
that that that um that business venture
with with the two other guys was very
shortlived um you know we we didn't
really mesh when it came to work ethic
and when it came to our goals so you
know that didn't work out so I I found
myself Al still trying to figure out how
to do this business so you know from
from that point it took me about another
year and a half you know still driving
Uber still still getting up at 3:00 in
the morning you know still um you know
struggling financially probably making
about two probably making about 1,200
bucks of a month eating peanut butter
jelly sandwiches but I still I still had
the I still had the vision I still had
the motivation so about a year and a
half I'm still figuring out I found
another buddy of mine and and I'm still
trying to put this business together I'm
like okay how can we put this business
together and so me and him me and him
get together I tell him the concept I'm
trying to do and he's like yeah let's
let's let's get together again another
short live situation and this one this
one kind of hurt because I thought I
thought this was the partner I needed
for this for this business and again
that didn't work so I had to I had I had
to kind of keep going back to the drum
board you know I kept driving Uber try
to figure things out and it's just as
they say third time is a charm the third
time was the charm and so you know I
finally I finally got back into it I'm
like you know I'm gonna do this business
if I have to do it by myself I'm gonna
figure this thing out and I did you know
I I got into it um you know I I I um I
signed up for this broker Academy um I
thought the broker Academy was going to
be was G to give me all the the
mentorship and the knowledge that I
needed uh come to find out you know was
a lot of people in there that didn't
have very much Integrity you know um no
one in that group was willing to give me
any kind of mentorship so everything
that I learned I learned through
mistakes um everything that I learned I
learned a few things maybe through
Google and and through YouTube and you
know um but I started putting things
together and and I started putting
things together you know I got out of
the group I decided you know what I can
learn more on my own than I can on this
group I feel like it wasn't really doing
anything and
um I I was still even though I had the
business I still was I still was kind of
stuck on the niche because I I wanted to
have I wanted to do this business but I
wanted to say I wanted to have a a
certain Niche that I did business with
and as as time went on I I I started
traveling in the city of Houston and I
started seeing I started seeing a lot of
construction projects I started seeing a
lot of these ground level projects and I
was like man I I think I got something
there so I became obsessed with
construction and construction projects I
started doing every I started doing
every single thing possible um to find
out how I could become a um Finance
person for these projects I started
contacting um construction project
managers
uh commercial real estate brokers all
these different things and U things
things started turning around for me you
know I it's it's one of those things you
just got to stick with something you
know and and and I did and and um you
know W and and I'm I'm just proud to say
you know Watson worldwide Capital you
know it's faed a lot of Trials you know
trying to you know took a took a while
try to figure things out figure out you
know the niche you know and um you know
how we was going to do business but um
you know I'm I'm proud that we was able
to kind of go through those things
because it was needed and you know uh
looking forward now you know we're we uh
we started off and and um you know here
in early early 2020 and you know we came
out doing you know projects overseas so
now we are um you know we have a couple
of projects in uh Puerto Rico uh the
Virgin Islands and
um and Columbia that we're working on
and um so that that that's that's
amazing and the thing about those
projects is those projects came out of
nowhere but I I knew I knew those
projects came from God because it
because I had I had just started doing I
had a prayer you know and and my prayer
was real detailed and and I and I told
him exactly what I wanted you know what
how I was willing to work and they came
and when these projects came these were
not million-dollar
projects these were $150 million
projects that they needed financing for
you know and they they came to they came
to Watson worldwide capital and so I'm
I'm just I'm just excited you know for
where we are right now and I'm just
excited that you know we we stayed the
course and for anybody that's you know
watching this broadcast you know tonight
I mean that's the main thing I would
just say is that you just have to stay
the course you know pain is one of the
things that you know you can't work
around you're G to have to you g to have
to go through some pain you know you're
going to have to
endure you know failures and sometimes
you're going to have a little bit of
self-doubt but you you can't you can't
self-doubt yourself too long you gotta
you got to just kind of be a little
discouraged just for a second but then
you got to just start getting back you
gotta you gotta you gotta pray you gotta
meditate whatever you need to do to get
yourself back on track because I will
tell you that it is worth it and that's
and that's one that's one of the main
reasons why I stayed with it so long you
know is because I knew it was worth it
and you know I had I had I had some
times you know when you know things
didn't really look like it was you know
going going in the right direction you
know which it may you know be like
sometimes you know I was you know I had
times when I was sitting there driving
Uber and I'm just and I'll be
questioning myself you know saying how
how long how much longer am I gonna keep
driving Uber you know what is it going
to take for me to you know not have to
drive Uber and and be a to build this
business but I I realized that you know
you know God did me a favor when he had
me doing Uber and and I didn't see it
when I first started and the and the
favor was Uber gave me the time and
flexibility to build a business because
I realized that in the past when I tried
to build businesses and I was working
you know between the between the twoh
hour commute a day you know leaving at 6
o'clock in the morning getting home at
7:30 you know it was just very very
tough to to start a business and so it
it was a blessing from God and it was
also a sacrifice on my part because I
could have easily went and got a job and
and the thing is is just you know
everybody wants to you know get a job
and and and know what you're gonna make
on a weekly monthly you know yearly
basis but I I I I I sacrific and I and I
bet on myself that you know no matter
how little it was I was going to do
every single thing possible to maximize
the situation because I knew it was
temporary right I mean like the fact
that you're betting on yourself what it
sounds like if we were to put the pieces
together that you know that your
learning disability just like with
dyslexia for me is that it has carried
throughout my whole life so a lot of
things that um a lot of things that
would take someone to would be able to
learn within one month or maybe a few
weeks I was learning within years but
once I learned it I understood it and
you nobody could you know break up my
flow because I I was practicing the
recipe because it took me a long time to
get even to the position that I was in
and I even had my own trials and
tribulations but from what it sounds
like it's like you know you you know
instinctively in yourself that you
believe in yourself enough to say Hey
you know I'm gonna try this out and I
don't care what it takes I don't care
how much time it takes because the one
thing you didn't mention is patience you
had all this patience for all this
time man
and you know and of course it's rough
but then you you said it yourself
gratitude like you Express gratitude to
God because you're saying hey you know
what even though you weren't in the
position that you were
in God gave you a a
car you had a roof over your head you
know what I mean you had somewhere yeah
you were crying because you had to eat
the the baloney sandwiches but you know
the fact is you you're in this position
now
where you're making millions of dollars
you're helping you're you're you're
You're Building um you're building
communities and and I like hats off for
you uh half hats off to you for such a
tremendous story of not giving up on
yourself now the lucky lady that you're
going to uh get married to was she uh
around during these uh phases that you
were going
through she she was um she was right
there and and the F the fun thing about
that is you know I I met her I met her a
year ago and the funny thing about it is
when I when I met her and we were just
friends and and um you know we were just
looking to do business we never even
thought about a relationship and the
funny thing about it
is when I when I when I when I first met
her I was having some really rough times
with Wasson worldwi capital and I was I
was tired you know mentally and
physically and I was getting ready to
just close the door you know on it and
she you know she she kind of questioned
me on on on um you know on U you know
giving up and you know on how you know
passionate I was about the business and
and so that that that really kept me
going and then it was it was again it
was just another another little
reflection but you know she's been a
great instrumental pieces for is um you
know the business I mean she's done a
lot of the you know a lot of our our
Graphics a lot of our you know you know
whether it's pictures whether whether
it's wording you know um any any any
areas that that I may struggle in you
know she has the the strength in and and
I and I and I just heard this a long
time ago I I don't know who it was but
they talking about you know I've seen so
many I've seen so many men where they
they on they're on the cusp of of being
successful but then when they when they
meet the right women it's like things
start to kind of line up and so you know
we we we we came in you know right on
time and everything so it's it's uh
definitely been great because you know
she was there when you know when I was
going through those struggles even when
I started back and I was and I was still
driving Uber and she you know I I
remember so many days when you know I
get up doing Uber and I make you know
$10 for the whole day and she's you know
kind of you know encouraging me to keep
going or you know encouraging me you
know yeah you made $10 but go go ahead
and and and work on your business and
you know it's kind of difficult doing
that because you know I mean I'm like
how many how many how many how many days
can I make $10 you know I got a and I
got different things coming up you know
I can only make $10 for one day I got to
make I got to start making more money
you know so uh but it but it's it's it's
definitely been great great experience
you know we're building a you know
Legacy here we're building a family
business and so it's uh definitely
exciting to uh be able to work
together that's that's amazing and she
was and you know because I've I've been
in situations where um people thought I
was crazy and I had to get out of
relationships because you know I I saw
the entrepreneur her life and the fact
that you had someone that supported you
um you know and I I'm not sure if she
supported you financially or if she
supported you mentally but you know the
fact that she saw something in you um so
much so to stick around because you know
there's a mantra out there especially
for for guys that aren't making a lot of
money or making $10 a day leave him you
know Wendy Williams will tell her
audience you know
leave right so it's the first because
you know especially in the black
community um a lot of women don't want
to be the struggle woman they don't want
to adapt to the struggle you know um
because they just feel and they they
feel that with their education and with
the positions that they are in life that
they don't want to support brothers that
are on the come up you know so what made
your your your is she your wife or wife
to be wife to be
wife to be so what what made her you
know look past that because that is a
stick in our community well I I I think
I think we when we met I think we both
had gone through so many bad
situations that the bad situations that
we went through really really matured us
and really you know had us to you know
self-reflect you know on what we wanted
and the things that we wanted it it it
mirrored we we wanted a lot of the the
same um the similar things we wanted a
lot of similar things and so you know we
both we both were in a transition and so
it it made it it made it that much
easier and and she was so she was so so
supportive along the way because you
know she encouraged me so much to really
focus on on the business and and and not
really worry about you know some of the
trials that was going on so she's really
a big a big um instrument in my faith
because you know we're we're so we're so
accustomed to look at the physical you
know what's what's in front of us what
we're going through what's what's due
and you know what we're struggling with
but to be able to look look past that
and look what's next and look at what we
what we what we be going through but
look at what that situation is is
teaching us and what that situation is
going to take us to so it's it's um it's
definitely been an amazing uh amazing
journey and
experience now tell me what it's like
being a father so you have a
newborn uh what is it like being a
father it's amazing um it's something
it's something that I've um looked
forward to for for a long time you know
I've always had this
desire um to be a family man to to have
a wife uh to have a to have children you
know so many lessons that I that I
learned you know along the way you know
through you know parents you know
through mentors through different
mentors that I had in my life and so I
was just I was very excited because I I
love to teach you know
and and I realize how tough it is being
a black in America you know and I I see
the different things that that go on and
so my my my thing is you know always
looking every every single day at what I
can possibly
teach to put him in POS put to put him
in the best position as a man to not
only be successful and and be the best
version of himself but to encourage him
to not be a a follower but but to be a
leader and to and to follow you know his
own mind and and not to look at a lot of
the things that he may run into whether
it's different peers of here different
peers of his and what they're doing but
really focus on what you want to do and
and look and look forward because
sometimes you can think that something
is cool but that one thing you do can
really really ruin your
life totally now I just wanted to shout
out to all the people that has um
that has come into this live uh Matthew
Riley shout out to you uh Steve and
anyone and in any of the groups that are
seeing this for the first time uh please
share this out share this out and um you
know this of course is brought to you by
uh my company bowai creative we are a uh
digital marketing company and I am the
brand Savant I develop and Implement
brand strategies that are coun intuitive
and they're powered by first principles
thinking so if you know anyone that's uh
looking for any type of uh branding
services or web development or graphic
design uh hit me up um I'll give you a
finder fee so um we we've we've gotten
to the end of this uh uh of the first
round of questioning we're gonna uh
enter into the the the lightning
realm sorry for for the sound effects
but you know I I'm still working on the
sound effects but but
um talking or
texting which which which one do you
prefer um
talking talking favorite favorite day of
the
week I'm I'm a be I mean I would say
Monday but you know being an
entrepreneur every day every day is
great you know I mean I'm not an
employee
anymore exactly because the employees
they you know Monday is their the worst
day Friday's the the greatest day and
I'm like man I don't got to I like for
me I work in my home I don't got to
leave nowhere so every day is a great
day um favorite city in the US besides
the one you live
in uh San Diego I'm born and
raised born and raised awesome and uh
nickname your parents used to call
you never really had a nickname to be
honest with
you okay it's all good uh would you
rather be able to speak every language
in the world or be able to talk to
animals uh speak every
language speak every language favorite
holiday uh Christmas I I love I love the
family time Family
bonding awesome awesome um how long does
it take for you to get
ready you mean get ready for like a
presentation
or just to go
out I say probably about 30
minutes 30 minutes okay and scale from
one to 10 how good are you a
driver 10 I mean obviously I had a lot
of
experience yeah most definitely um and
fill in the blank oh no we'll switch
that question Michael Jackson or
Prince uh Michael
Jackson Michael Jackson okay and
invisibility or or super
strength super
strength awesome and the last question
is it wrong for vegans to eat animal
crackers
no it's not wrong okay awesome well um
Antoine thank you so much for um telling
us your story I mean I think that you
know what you've what what you've what
you went through and how you've
persevered in every part of your life I
think um I think that's that's amazing
and there's something that everyone can
learn from because not everyone needs to
you know be born with a silver spoon in
their mouth not everyone needs to be
born with smarts in order to be
successful and you are a you know a
great example of a successful individual
that is a father that you know that is
going to get married and that has a good
it sounds like you have a good Network
you have a good uh circle of influence
and you have a good support system and
so you know thank you so much uh brother
for for for coming into this uh uh this
broadcast today um and H how was your
experience with go live and
prosper amazing experience um again I
thank you for the opportunity
uh for being on the show um I was going
to tell you uh U my my son is is is
actually six not a
newborn oh sorry I didn't mean I I
thought you had a new it said you had a
new son in the notes so I uh didn't
didn't realized I should have been a
little more detailed than that yeah
yeah
yeah yeah he came from my
fiance okay okay okay so um yeah and I
have a I have 11-year-old and uh and I
think that you know the things that you
said in terms of what you want to
instill in him you know I think that
it's I think it's it's imperative like
for especially for fathers to to put in
those those lessons so that
children have that grounding because I
for for example me as a as a as a parent
I don't I I tell my son I'm like hey I'm
not your best
friend I am here to be the best father
that I can be so I'm gonna tell you all
the things even the stuff that you may
not see me do I'm G to tell you all the
good things because even if you decide
to you know go into another Direction in
your life you at least have the pillars
and the foundations um to support your
life you know what I mean and the fact
that you know I think that I want I want
my son to see this interview because you
know again it's just to show another man
that has decided to just not give up on
himself you bet you bet all your chips
on yourself and I think that's amazing
brother you know you are an inspiration
and I think that you should are do you
do speaking engagements you talking to
kids and and and and whatnot you know
that's funny um I I actually used to do
that um kind of kind of in my earlier
days I was I was doing a lot more
speaking back then um um but over over
the over the last you know so many years
I I decided to do more business so I was
I've been more business focused but but
of course you know I'm kind of working
my way towards that because I definitely
I definitely have a message you know um
I I'm I'm a big believer and in
self-discipline you know I'm a big
believer in consistency I'm a big
believer in faith you know um knowing
your vision so there there's a lot of
there's a lot of principles and and I
always and I always tell them that you
know the most important thing you have
to have and the thing that that I had to
have is I had to have a lot of mentors
around me you have to have people around
you that that not only believe in you
but people just going to hold you
accountable people is gonna kind of push
you uh past past your comfort and past
you know past past your
pain I I do have one question for you if
you were to go back to your young self
what would what would you what would you
ask what would you tell that young
self honestly I would tell my young self
not to listen
to what the school district or school
system said I was going to be because in
their eyes they saw me as below average
as their in their eyes they saw me never
succeeding never doing any any of the
things that I that I started doing was
started doing in the things I'm doing
now but God had a different plan and he
was just equi me and taking me through
all those challenges and those in the
journey that I had to go on to get to
I'm at right
now God had another plan and obviously
that plan worked out my brother so thank
you antoan for coming into the hustle
Zone uh and uh coming in to go live and
prosper uh and um the the last thing
that I that I would uh need you to do is
um I'm going to do a call and response
I'm G to say welcome to the and I need
you to scream as loud as you can without
waking anybody up hustle zone so welcome
to the hustle Zone hustle Zone okay so
try it again but this time with a little
bit more
enthusiasm but okay so welcome to the
hustle
Zone thank you so much my
brother I'm sorry tell your wife I'm
sorry I didn't mean
to scream scream so loud but thank you
again for your story and um and folks if
you guys are watching this and you
missed it you you be able to hear this
interview on Google Play on Spotify and
um and apple music and is there and how
how do we find you um they can connect
with me on on Facebook we're at Watson
worldwide Capital that's our business
page uh definitely connect with us uh
definitely reach out to us let us know
um if you have any projects going on
that you you know looking to to get
funded because not only do fund projects
but we also facilitate the projects so
making sure that everything is right or
and also too there's people out there um
they may be looking to do um joint
venture Partnerships uh Equity
Partnerships so we we do that as
well awesome awesome and ALS and also
also we also our LinkedIn page as
well okay and so sorry can you spell out
your I'm just gonna put it on the screen
here so people can
see um well actually it won't allow me
to do it but
here actually no we got it here so
what's the the correct
spelling of your website oh um it's a
Watson w w TS o
n and then it's a u World w w r l l d w
d
and uh no it's um this is our business
our business page we're actually uh
relaunching our website right now
okay awesome so um so it's uh Watson
worldwide capital and capital and what's
the what's what's after the
dot um for the website
address no no it's it's it's a Facebook
it's a Facebook business page oh it's a
Facebook page sorry I misunderstood okay
so folks make sure to check them out
they're just revamping their their their
their website but you can see us uh you
can see them at um hold on one second
here let me just hide
that in it's Capital it's it's the ca
capap I
um my dyslexia coming in my brother
sorry about that okay oh no I put the
wrong one in there okay is that is that
correct that's it okay sorry but we'll
edit this out most of this is just the
pre-recording so once that it's all all
the the little uh funky stuff gets
edited out but um thank you again uh for
uh for for coming in and I will talk to
you later my friend thank you for having
me okay have a good one so folks that
was a great interview again another
story of an individual that you know
against the odds that he faced was able
to Triumph through and and create a
awesome um uh business for himself and
for his family you know and you know the
one of the themes that I'm starting to
hear with a lot of people is that they
want to build generational wealth and
and that's what it sounds like this
brother is doing um him and his family
and you know it was great to have him on
so if you guys are looking to um you
know um if you want to get any advice
for him um or you want to ask him some
questions make sure to go to his
Facebook page at Watson worldwide
capital
uh uh uh check him out on Facebook there
and then folks if you guys are looking
for web design uh for graphic design or
any of those type of services make sure
to go to
ww.bbc creative.com and if you want to
be on this show uh go live and prosper
make sure to send me uh a personal
message and I will send you the booking
link for um uh so that you can uh uh uh
book yourself for the next show so thank
you guys so much for for tuning in and I
will talk to you guys later peace